papaclassifieds.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy -

**Our Privacy Policy sets out our practices with respect to the ads collection,our conents, use and disclosure of personal information in connection with Papaclassifieds.com . This Privacy Policy may be updated by us at any time by posting on the site without any prior notice.   
Also, this Privacy Statement may be supplemented or modified by agreements entered into between us and an individual from time to time. In this Privacy Statement, personal information means any information about an identifiable individual, including contact and demographic details, not including collective information or information regarding a group in summarized form.**

We can be contacted via e-mail at [Contact Us](http://papaclassifieds.com/contact/)...

**For each and all visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes information of your browser, IP address, City/State/Country.**

**We collect only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our Web page, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail.**

**The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our site page for each individual visitor.**

**  
Collection of Personal Information  
The Site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (such as name and email address) and demographic information (such as postal code, age, or income level) and other information that is used by us to provide services.**

** Disclosure of Personal Information  
We may disclose certain personal information as follows:  
\- by publishing ads either online and/or in print, as the case may be, in connection with items that are for sale by customers  
\- to third party service providers and to affiliated entities in order to carry out work on our behalf,  
\- to law enforcement agencies for the purposes of investigating fraud or other offences, or  
\- to legal, financial, and other professional advisors or in connection with the sale or reorganization of all or part of its business or operations.  
\- By having your mobile number listed on clickindia.com, you agree to receive communication from third parties who may wish to contact you through the site.  
Except as provided above, we will not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required or permitted by law.  
**

** Cookies and IP Addresses  
We may use your IP address to identify you and your membership, gather broad demographic information about our users, diagnose problems with our server, and administer the Site. The Site uses cookies to keep track of your membership tools and to make sure you do not see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site. We also provide an option to log out should you be using an insecure or publicly shared computer.  
We use outside ad companies to display ads on the Site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of the Site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information.  
**

**Links  
This Site contains links to other websites, such as websites providing national search capabilities and information resources designed to inform buyers and sellers about general aspects of property that is being sold. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Please ensure you review the privacy policies of the websites that you visit.  
**

**Security  
We protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information with security measures appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. However, it is possible that any information transmitted via the Internet may be intercepted by unknown third parties. We use Verisign to have credit card data transmitted to our network servers in a secure encrypted mode.  
**

**Opt-Out  
When appropriate, users of the Site are given the opportunity to (i) opt-out of receiving communications from us, (ii) remove their information from our database, or (iii) elect to no longer receive services from us. If you wish to opt-out of receiving further communications, please contact us.**
